youriding.com 2015-02-06

# YouRiding - Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

At Intellysurf we share your concerns about privacy while using our website, www.youriding.com (the "Site" or "YouRiding"). Accordingly we want you to understand what types of information we are collecting and what may happen to that information. This Privacy Policy details how we safeguard the privacy of our on-line users and does not apply to information that may be collected by us off-line. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the YouRiding Terms of Use. Your use of YouRiding and any personal information you provide through YouRiding remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.

**WHAT YOU WILL FIND IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

* How we collect information about you  
* How we use or share information about you  
* How we safeguard information about you  
* Other matters related to the information we collect about you

**COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**

Information is collected from our users at several different points during your use of YouRiding. In general, information is collected in connection with the purchase of goods or services though our on-line stores, surveys, newsletters, user registrations for products, services, warranties, contests or for on-line game participation, message boards, and complaints or third party communications we may receive regarding our users.

**Registration:** To use some resources available through YouRiding, a user must complete our registration process. During registration, a user is required to provide certain categories of information, which may include a name, address, e-mail address, and a password.

**Optional Information:** At various other points during your use of YouRiding, you may be asked to provide information about yourself. For example, you may wish to participate in a survey or a contest. Participation in surveys or contests or the use of other services which require the input of additional information is completely voluntary on your part, and you have the choice about whether to disclose the information necessary to use these features of our site. Users purchasing products or services through our on-line stores will be required to provide additional information such as a valid credit card number, expiration date, and shipping and billing addresses.

**Passive Collection of Information:** In addition to the information which you actively provide to us by methods such as completing the registration form, we collect information about how you interact with YouRiding. We collect passive information for purposes such as testing and improving a user's experience with YouRiding and the compilation of broad aggregate demographic data and related usage information for internal purposes and for disclosure to third parties such as advertisers and content partners. The types of passive information collected by this site include, without limitation, your IP address, which type of browser you are using, where you go within YouRiding and your behavior within YouRiding.

**Cookies:** When you visit the Site, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Site may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

**Collection of Information from Children:** Intellysurf abides by French law and the guidelines set up by the Commission Nationale de l'Informatique et des Libertés (CNIL) regarding youth privacy. As such, we will not knowingly collect any personal information from or allow the registration of young people under the age of 13.

**USE / SHARING OF INFORMATION**

We may use your information in order to deliver products and services to you and to customize YouRiding to your interests and enhance your overall experience with YouRiding. We try to recognize you using various methods, including having you log in with your user name and your password. Once we recognize you advertisements and other content may be customized for you so that you can see what interests you the most. In addition, as described above, we utilize passive information to learn more about how you interact with YouRiding. This passive information may be combined with your other information for purposes such as testing and improving your experience at our site and the compilation of broad aggregate demographic data and related usage information for internal purposes and for disclosure to third parties such as advertisers and content partners. This aggregate passive information does not contain any personal information which can identify any individual user.

We may use your contact information periodically in order to send you e-mail regarding updates to YouRiding and to alert you or remind you of happenings related to YouRiding. The frequency of these messages will vary depending upon various factors.

We will not knowingly sell, share, rent or otherwise transfer your information other than in accordance with the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy. We do not share any information that can be tied to you without your permission. If you give your permission to allow third parties to contact you, personal information about you (such as your contact information and other information collected during your visit to YouRiding) may be shared with data aggregators, marketers (possibly in the form of list rental), and other organizations. Regardless of your decision regarding the sharing of your personal information, we may share broad aggregate demographic data and related usage information with our business partners. This aggregate information does not contain any personal information which can identify any individual user.

From time to time, we may decide that it is more efficient to use third parties to perform specific services, such as sending communications to our users. If we use a third party to provide specific services (such as sending communications to our users on our behalf), then information (such as contact information) may be shared with that party to the extent necessary for the third party to provide these services. These third party service providers are only allowed to use personally identifiable information for the purpose of providing the specific services requested by us. The third party services covered by this paragraph do not include links to third party sites found on our site, which are governed by a more specific provision below.

While we strive to protect the personal information of our users, we will release personal information if required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary or appropriate.

Our sites may also have message boards or chat areas, where users can exchange ideas and communicate with one another. When posting to a message board or chat area, please be aware that the information is being made publicly available on-line and any user does so at his or her own risk.

**SECURITY**

We have security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse and/or unauthorized alteration of the information under our control. You are the only user authorized to update your profile, unless you provide your password information to another party.

We utilize both online and offline security methods, including firewalls, passwords and restricted physical access to the places where your information is stored to help protect personally identifiable information. Our staff is trained to comply with our security procedures, and our security procedures are regularly reviewed and revised, if necessary, by our privacy team.

If you have any questions about security issues at our site, please contact us at [contact@youriding.com](mailto:contact@youriding.com), and we will try to answer your questions.

**OTHER PROVISIONS**

YouRiding is hosted in France and is intended for and directed to users in France. If you are a user accessing YouRiding from the European Union, America, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from French laws, please be advised that through your continued use of YouRiding, which is governed by French law, this Privacy Notice, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to France and you consent to that transfer.

Your use of YouRiding indicates an acceptance of the terms of the Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to update or amend this Privacy Policy at any time.

In the event that we sell, assign or transfer some or all of our business to a successor or acquirer, we may sell, assign or transfer all of your information, regardless of your opt status, to such successor or acquirer.

YouRiding may contain links to other third party sites, applications or content. Please be aware that we do not exercise control over the information, applications, products, services or policies of third parties accessible through YouRiding. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave YouRiding and to read the privacy policies of each and every third party that may be providing sites, applications or content linked to YouRiding. This Privacy Policy applies solely to the information collected by us on-line through YouRiding.

Your privacy is important to us. If you have questions about any of the provisions described above, please contact us at [contact@youriding.com](mailto:contact@youriding.com).
